kapanga.net 2017-12-03

# Kapanga Softphone

### Information Collection and Use

Ecotronics is the sole owner of the information collected on this web site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any manner that differs from that which is disclosed herein. Ecotronics collects information from users (at the discretion of users) at several points within the company's web site.

### Information Request Forms

Ecotronics requests information from prospects or clients at several points within our web site, asking for information such as name, phone number, e-mail address, company, etc. This information is used for internal purposes only and to correspond directly with clients for whom we provide services.

### Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the web site, track users' movements, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

### Aggregate Data Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual or corporation. Though this information is not personally identifiable, Ecotronics will share it only with organizations that have established effective privacy policies.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Ecotronics is not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies exclusively to information collected by this web site.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information that a web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make a web site more useful by allowing the site to personalize information for visitors and by storing information about customer preferences on a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers.

### Notification of Changes

If at any point the Ecotronics privacy policy undergoes any change, those changes will be posted on our web site's home page so that users will always be aware of what information we collect and how we use it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via e-mail. Users will then be free to determine if they wish to allow us to use their information in this updated manner.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy or the security of this web site, please contact privacy[at]kapanga.net.
